# Wing J. Har

Full-Stack Developer

winghar@outlook.com https://linkedin.com/in/winghar 646 823-7333 New York, NY, 11101, US

Experienced Full-Stack Developer and Product Manager with a background in modernizing coding architecture, driving product development, and executing successful marketing strategies. Skilled in JavaScript, RoR, SQL, Agile, SCRUM, and product methodologies.

## **Work Experience**

## **Full-Stack Developer**

Sep 2021 - Present

FBS Data Financial Business Systems, Inc. | Remote

Worked with logical coding languages such as JavaScript, RoR, SQL, and various JavaScript frameworks such as StimulusJS in order to modernize archaic coding architecture, fix bugs, create new features for clients, and maintain a high resolved tasks to issues ratio.

- Utilized SQL queries and Database tools such as mongoDB, mySQL, DIG, DBeaver, and Kibana in order to confirm accurate
  data from front-end to back-end, as well as obtain back-end data for research.
- Took ownership of the Print and PDF issues and repository regarding princeXML third-party integration, removing 90% of the print and PDF related issues, and lowering future related issues by another 90%.
- Utilized archaic custom programming language in order to resolve tasks and modernized this language through the use of JavaScript and modern JavaScript frameworks.
- Developed and created new features for FlexMLS with a focus on customer success, based on user feedback, as well as gathering all information from users before beginning a project.
- Designed and executed Training Programs for code best practices, resulting in increased code efficiency and readability.
- Part of the CREATE mentorship program, teaching people how to program and worked on building software applications, utilizing different frameworks and libraries, such as React.js, Bootstrap, and MongoDB or mySQL for database.
- Applied knowledge of Scaled Agile Framework to manage software development lifecycle effectively, reducing potential risks and enhancing project outcomes as a Full-Stack Developer.
- Brought to company attention innovative solutions to get past market thresholds, including the usage of advanced technology
  in Machine Learning, and the creation of a company application PoC which uses machine learning to predict and forecast
  housing market patterns by location and other data entry points.
- Developed strong team communication skills through Slack, and build a solid teamwork foundation which led to mentoring new programming prospects.

#### **Digital Marketing Specialist**

Feb 2019 - Aug 2021

Product Gym | New York City, New York

Took ownership in the digital marketing of Product Gym with daily activities such as market research, competitive research, and creation (and presentation) of ideas and new marketing schemas to co-founders of the company.

- Created new innovative ways to keep audience retention including automated webinars and online events, as well as created new products for the members after competitive market analysis and risk factor calculations.
- Created and managed company social medias, media tags, and analyzed optimal times of each day to begin marketing advertisements to increase audience clickthrough rate from 40% to 65%.
- Enhanced website SEO and clickthrough rate, as well as analyzed website hot spots to best focus and target the optimal user experience flow, increasing the number of sales calls and onboarding by 25% through market funnel.
- Increase audience attention by 25% through the creation of a marketing funnel to simplify UX workflow and streamlined the flow of users to sales.
- Demonstrated expertise in defining requirements and trends in the market, translating business needs into actionable development plans and tasks to increase audience retention, satisfaction, and experience.

 Successfully translated Business Goals into technical requirements needed for presentation on the marketing side, to present to clients and stakeholders.

### **Product Manager of Engineering and Data Systems**

Product Gym | New York City, New York

Feb 2019 - Aug 2021

Led cross-functional teams and ensured the product life cycle from beginning to end, from the creation and ideology of a new product or feature to the presentation of it to the public, through market knowledge and engineering knowledge.

- Implemented efficient code for back-end Development Work leading to a 15% improvement in application performance.
- Consistently collaborated with team members on Development Work, utilizing Agile methodologies to ensure project success.
- Developed plans and documentation for innovative future features, including an A.I. chatbot which uses Machine Learning methodologies. and third-party workflow integrations using DRIP. Resulted in a 95% increase in members and a 40% decrease in support helpdesk calls.
- Developed and utilize A|B testing in order to garner feedback from users in order to develop strategic ways to improve customer success and satisfaction with the webapp.
- Managed complex projects by defining requirements, receiving and using customer feedback, and ensuring clear communication between business stakeholders and the technical team.

### **Full Stack Developer Intern**

Mar 2019 - Aug 2019

Hollywood Insider | Remote

Developed the Hollywood Insider website fully from front-end and back-end with the support of the Product and Design teams, as well as other developers on modifications to the website based upon their specifications.

- Developed side websites and design templates for Hollywood Insider, utilizing a variety of tools from PHP, CSS, HTML,
   Javascript for front-end development, and PHP, SQL, and mySQL for the database for backend (LAMP Stack).
- Helped work on the main website's backend and infrastructure at Hollywood Insider.
- Received side projects to work on and communicated effectively with the team over at Hollywood Insider on a regular basis for work updates.

## References

#### Pritan Ambroase (Hollywood Insider CEO)

Created a reference letter for me after my departure from Hollywood Insider for my developer skills. On-hand and will send over if requested.

### **Richard Chen and Cody Chang**

Co-Founders of Product Gym and whom I had worked closely with in executing successful product and feature launches for the company to the market and seeing it thrive from a small start-up of 5 people to over 50.

Will provide reference details if requested.

#### **Todd Holdman**

Full-Stack Developer manager at FBS (Financial Business Systems, Inc.)

Will provide reference details if requested.

#### Core Skills

HTML, JavaScript, CSS, React, StimulusJS, SQL, mySQL, MongoDB, Kibana, JIRA, MIRO, Trello, Agile, SCRUM, Product Development, Marketing, Market Research, Customer Service, UX, UI, Product Roadmap, Competitive Analysis, Google Analytics, Market Analysis, KPI, Risk Management, QA, Back-End Development, Front-End Development, Product Management, Workflow Documentation, Technical Development, Third-Party Integrations, SaaS Platform, External Market Research, Kanban

# **Education**

## **CUNY College of Staten Island**

Sep 2017 - May 2021

Bachelor of Science Computer Science

# Languages

English (fluent), Mandarin (intermediate)

## **Awards**

Dean's List Jul 2020

CUNY College of Staten Island

Dean's List Award associated with the City University of New York - College of Staten Island.

## **Certificates**

Google Analytics 31/08/2019

Google